<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lee Yousef &amp; Associates Real Estate Video Blog</title>
    <description>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Calgary Area Real Estate Market</description>
    <link>blog.leeyousef.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="blog.leeyousef.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 10:21:02 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 10:21:02 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Come Learn What Sets Us Apart</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4xXC5cBe79M&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to take a minute to talk about our team and what you can expect from our information session on October 6th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early on, our agents were asked to convert typical cold Internet leads with minimal success and administrative support. After many months of trial and error, I realized that we needed to find a better way. Most teams can generate cold Internet leads, and if that’s what you want, there’s no shortage of teams in Calgary that offer that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for a complete approach to reinventing your real estate career, then we are the team for you. We all know what we need to do on a daily basis, but it’s very difficult to do it on your own. &lt;strong&gt;You need time, money, training, and a lot of systems to get it done. Above all, you need a dedicated team of people who are working together toward the same goal.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We don't just teach you; we grow with you.%20blog.leeyousef.com/come-learn-what-sets-us-apart.html%20via%40leeyousef&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We don’t just teach you; we grow with you.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like most new agents, when I started in real estate, I was trying anything and everything I could get my hands on. There is no shortage of ideas out there, and that’s why we designed our training programs and systems to only focus on activities that produce results. We cover everything from transcripts to marketing to presentation skills and how to get commitments from buyers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We don’t just teach you how to do it, we also work with you on a day to day basis to help you make sure it gets done.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever considered working in a positive, supportive, and financially stable work environment, you need to come to our information session on October 6th. We’ll talk about the details of what our team offers and what it takes to be successful in real estate today. No catch, no gimmicks. Don’t waste any more money looking for resources and additional ideas to grow your business – come see how we do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a handful of agents and space is limited. If you share our vision and you’d like to learn more about what we do, come see us October 6th. If you have any further questions, feel free to reach out to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://leeyousefrecruitme.wixsite.com/joinourteam/join-our-team&quot;&gt;RSVP here to the October 6th event.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>blog.leeyousef.com/come-learn-what-sets-us-apart.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">blog.leeyousef.com/come-learn-what-sets-us-apart.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate Training Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
